因此，您应该在此点安装 Docker Desktop for MAC 和
So you should have Docker Desktop
installed at this point for MAC and
Windows 。
Windows.
没有 Docker Desktop for Linux，
There is no Docker Desktop for Linux,
在这种情况下，您将需要没有 GUI的 Docker 引擎。
in which case you'll need Docker
engine which doesn't have a GUI.
您可以在此查看此小 Docker 鲸将位于系统托盘中的底部
You can see here this little Docker whale
will be at the bottom in the system tray
如果你在 Windows中
if you're in Windows.
您可以在此处看到 Docker Desktop 正在运行。
You can see here I have
Docker Desktop running.
接下来我想了解的是 Docker Hub。
The next thing I wanna get you more
acquainted with is Docker Hub.
所以你可以去 hub.docker.com。
So you can just go to hub.docker.com.
这可能是 Docker的最佳部分之一，
This is probably one of
the best parts about Docker,
它们基本上是用这些节点的术语，然后是晚上的容器的，对吧 ?
is that they basically made these node
terms and then npm for containers, right?
所以我可以说， Docker，给我一个 MongoDB 容器
So I can just say hey, Docker,
give me a MongoDB container and
你只要把它放下
you just pull it down.
它开始运行它知道它应该做的一切
It starts running it and
it knows everything it's supposed to do.
那是个黑盒对吧
It's a bit of a black box, right?
我不知道它在车篷下面做什么
I don't know exactly what it's
doing underneath the hood,
我只知道它是蒙古人的
I just know that it runs Mongo.
太棒了
And that's great!
我不想知道怎么跑蒙戈如果你知道怎么跑曼戈
Cuz I didn't wanna know how to run Mongo,
if you know how to run Mango,
你真希望你不知道怎么跑蒙戈
you wish you didn't know how to run Mongo,
right, one of those things.
它有，我要说成千上万个容器，对吧 ?
And it has, I'm gonna say thousands and
tenths of thousands of containers, right?
你可以看到这里有来自甲骨文的官员
So you can see here it has
official ones from Oracle,
有正式的 MySQL 库奇库 DB2吗
has an official MySQL one,
Couch Base, DB2?
是否有人使用 DB2?
Does anyone use DB2?
我爸是个 DB2 推销员那是真实的故事
My dad was a DB2 salesman,
that's true story.
这就是为什么我在电脑周围长大的原因。
That's why I grew up around computers.
我不知道为什么我认为有必要分享，但分享时间。
I don't know why I thought that was
necessary to share but it's sharing time.
是的，你可以看到这里有什么东西。
[LAUGH] Yeah, you can see here
there's literally anything.
所以如果我输入蒙戈你会看到蒙哥的正式人来了
So if I type Mongo, you'll see that the
official Mongo one comes up right here and
你可以看到这个已经下载了一千万次了，所以几次。
you can see this has been downloaded
10 million times, so a few times.
如果你愿意的话就可以为账户报名了
So feel free to sign up for
an account if you want to.
它是免费的没有理由不去
It's free, there's no reason not to.
我有一个
I have one.
我已经出版了一个容器，我们今天将在课堂上使用。
And I have published one container which
we will be using during the class today.
但如果我在这里说 " docker mongo : 3 " ，就像这样
But that's when if I go in here and
say docker mongo:3 like this,
这就是我需要摆脱的地方
that's where, I need to get out of this.
所以你现在可以和这个环境做了，所以我们可以安全地退出它。
So you can be done with this environment
now so we can safely exit out of it.
所以就这样
Hence, just so
你知道你是否退出了整个环境对吧
you know if you do exit out of it you've
thrown away the entire environment, right?
因为容器一旦关闭就会消失在醚中
Because containers, once you close them,
disappear into the ether,
他们什么都没救
they don't save anything.
让我们来看看
So let's just see,
如果您输入 Docker ps ，那么它会显示所有正在运行的容器。
if you type docker ps it'll show you
all your containers that are running.
如果 Docker 不工作，您会看到错误消息，
If your Docker is not working,
you'll see an error message,
如果你想跑码头它会解决的
if you try to run docker ps,
it'll fix that.
如果我说码头拉风 3 它就会
And if I say docker
pull mongo:3 it's gonna
可以从 Docker 集线器中获取此信息，对吗 ?
go get this off of Docker hub, right?
会看起来像这样
It'll look something like this.
你可以再看一次我只是提醒你
So you can see, again,
I'm just reminding you,
有些容器挺大的
some of these containers are quite big.
这个是 117 兆字节。
This one is 117 megabytes.
所以让这个在背景中跑出来，好，再，
So let that run in the background for
a little bit, so yeah, again,
有 Docker 容器可以做任何事对吗
there's Docker containers for
just about anything, right?
有个节点，有个给鲁比，还有一个。
There's ones for node, there's ones for
Ruby, there's one for Go.
只有你能想象出的任何东西
There's just about anything you can
imagine someone's probably built
一个 Docker 容器，对吗 ?
a Docker container for, right?
当你需要一个模块时就像节点一样
It's like node when you're writing
something if you need a module,
机会是有人写的模块，你可以在 npm 上安装。
chances are someone's written that
module and you can just npm install it.
在这种情况下，我们可以为此使用 Docker Hub 。
In this case,
we can use Docker Hub for this.
所以在你开始建造自己的个体容器之前
So before you start going and building
your own bespoke artisanal containers,
检查 Docker Hub 是否首先具有此信息。
check out to see if
Docker Hub has it first.